Brayan Carreño

Front-end Developer

As a self-taught developer, I've been studying and improving my skills as a developer for two years. I appreciate challenges and Goals that push me to learn new things and improve my abilities. I enjoy making things utilizing JavaScript/TypeScript technologies that help people accomplish their duties more easily and quickly.

Cúcuta, Colombia +57 312 568 1362 andrescptrc.dev @andrescptrc on GitHub Brayan Carreño on Linkedin andrebrayan74@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Front-end Developer @ Devsu

SEP 2022 - PRESENT

Tasks involving this role

Development and maintenance of applications built with NextJs.

Refactoring and improvement of the app.

Integrate functionalities with services from Firebase, Algolia, etc.

Integrate scrapping functionalities.

Increase test coverage and apply TDD.

Front-end Developer @ EDteam

MAY 2021 - SEP 2022

Tasks involving this role

Development and maintenance of applications built with NextJs.

Change the login flow between the static web and the app.

Refactoring and improvement of the main app.

Improvements in the purchase flow of subscriptions.

Migration of the main app to TypeScript.

EDUCATION

Universidad de Pamplona - Software Engineering

FEB 2018 - PRESENT

ONLINE EDUCATION

JavaScript Moderno Guía Definitiva @ Udemy

Issued Feb, 2021 - ID UC-a1c353f6-6bb4-403c-8e2b-4ca2d0a984d1

INTERESTS

Learn new technologies and improve my skills.

SKILLS / ABILITIES

Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS/SASS

Libraries & Frameworks: Tailwind, React.js, Next.js, Redux, React Query and Jest.

Tools & Platforms: Git, Vercel, Node.js, MongoDB, Postgres, Firebase and Algolia.

LANGUAGES

Spanish - Native

English - B1